Let it go. It's not a big deal.
别再争好吗? 这又没什么大不了的
Not a big deal? It's amazing. You reach in,there's one maneuver and bam!
没什么大不了?这简直是太神奇了 你太妄下断语了,用点小技巧
A bra. Right out the sleeve.
钮盖胸罩从袖子出来
As far as I know,guys don't do anything that comes close. Right?
就我而言男生简单没得比 我说得对不对?
Come on! You guys can pee standing up.
拜托，男生可以站着尿
We can? Okay,I'm trying that.
我们行吗?我倒要试试看
Know what blows my mind?
知道什么最令我嫉妒?
Women can see breasts anytime they want.
女人随时都可以看自己的胸部
You look down, and there they are.
低头一看…它就在那里
How you get any work done is beyond me.
真搞不懂你们怎么会有心工作
I don't get how guys can do so many mean things...
知道我搞不懂什么吗? 男人可以做许多下流的事…
...and not even care.
…却能毫不在乎
-Multiple orgasms! -There you go.
多重高潮
The One With the East German Laundry Detergent
六人行 第1季 第05集 洗衣服
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
Saturday night. The big night!
了不起,周末夜,重要的夜晚
Date night! Saturday night. Saturday night!
约会的夜晚…周末夜…
-No plans,huh? -Not a one!
- 没有计划是吗? - 一个都没有
Not even breaking up with Janice?
连和珍妮丝分手的打算都没有?
Right,right. Shut up.
对…闭嘴
Chandler,nobody likes breaking up with someone.
钱德，没有人喜欢分手
Except for Kevin Millmore, may he rot in hell.
凯文.米勒除外，愿他在地狱里烂掉
-You just gotta do it. -I know. But it's just so hard.
-你明白的 -我知道,但是这确实太难了
You're sitting there with her. She has no idea.
你坐在她身旁…而她却一无所知
You finally get up the courage to do it.
最后你鼓起勇气
There's that awkward moment when you've handed her the note.
在这实在尴尬的时刻 当你将纸条拿给她・
You try to run out of the restaurant before she's finished the note.
在她看完纸条之前,你尝试着跑出饭店
Why do you have to break up with her? Be a man. Just stop calling.
干嘛分手?…争气点，不再打电话就行了
If you want,I'll do it with you.
如果愿意，我和你一起做
She'd feel like we're ganging up on her.
谢了，但这样她会认为 我们是联手来对付她
You dump Janice, I'll dump T ony.
你和珍妮丝分手 我和东尼分手
-You're breaking up with T ony? -He's sweet,but it's not fun anymore.
-东尼?你要和东尼分手? -他人很好.但是我对他再没新鲜感了
I don't know if it's me or his hunger strike,I don't know.
我不知道问题是在于我 还是他的绝食抗议
Do you want anything else?
还有人需要什么吗?
You had a nutty,chocolate-y, kind of cake-y,pie thing that
你做了有核果，巧克力之类的派…
Nothing. I' m fine.
没事，我还好
What's wrong? Why so scrunchie?
怎么啦,怪怪的
My father wants to give me a Mercedes convertible.
是我爸…他要买奔驰敞篷车给我
That guy,he burns me up.
那家伙真叫我生气
Yeah,it's a Mercedes if I move back home.
如果想要奔驰我就得搬回家了
It was horrible! He called me "young lady. "
太可恶了…他称我为“年轻的女士”
I hate when my father calls me that.
我最受不了我爸这样叫我
Did he say "You' re not up to this" again?
他是不是又说你年纪太轻之类
I got the extended version with choruses of...
对,他在这次加长版中说了三次…
... "You'll Never Make it on Your Own. "
…“你不可能独立”
Hi,Joey.
嘿,乔伊
Oh,my God! Angela!
天呀,安吉拉
Wow! Being dumped by you agrees with her.
被你甩掉对她大有好处
-Are you gonna go over there? -No. Yeah. No.
-你想过去吗? -不,我不
Okay,but not yet. I don't wanna seem too eager.
不,我不.我不想显得太想过去了
One Mississippi,two Mississippi...
一个密西西比,两个密西西比
...three Mississippi. That seems pretty cool.
…三个密西西比.那看起来真酷
-Hey,Angela. -Joey.
-安吉拉 -乔伊
You look good.
你看起来不错
That's because l' m wearing a dress that accents my boobs.
因为我的衣服突显出我的胸部
You don't say.
看得出来
So,Rachel,what are you doing tonight?
瑞秋，你今晚有何节目?
Big glamour night. Me and Monica at Launderama.
精彩丰富，我要和摩妮卡去洗衣店
You wanna hear a freakish coincidence? Guess who's doing laundry there too?
想知道有个巧合吗? 猜猜谁也要去洗衣店?
-Who? -Me!
-谁? -我
Was that not clear?
难道还不够清楚?
Why don't...?
何不…
Why don't I just join you both there?
何不让我加入你们?
Don't you have a laundry room in your building?
你的公寓没有洗衣间吗?
Yes.
是的
I do have a laundry room in my building.
有，我的公寓有洗衣间
But there's a rat problem.
但是现在有老鼠了
Apparently,they're attracted to dryer sheets.
它们显然对烘干机里的香香纸感兴趣
They're going in fine, but they're coming out all fluffy.
进入时还好 出来是却毛绒绒的
-Anyway,7-ish? -Sure.
-7点左右见? -好的
-Forget it. I' m with Bob now. -Bob? Who the hell's Bob?
-免了,我现在和鲍伯交往 -鲍伯?谁是鲍伯?
Bob is great. He's smart, sophisticated,and he has a real job.
鲍伯简直是棒透了 聪明，成熟，又有真正的工作
You go on three auditions a month and you' re an actor. Bob
你每个月面试三次就称自己是演员 但是鲍伯
Come on! We were great together.
我们在一起时很开心
And not just at the fun stuff, but,like,talking too.
不只是寻欢作乐我们也聊得来
Sorry,Joey. You said, " Let's be friends. " So guess what?
抱歉,乔伊 你曾说我们当朋友就好,那么
-What? -We' re just friends.
-什么? -我们只是朋友
Fine. Fine.
行
Why don't the four of us have dinner tonight? As friends.
我们四个何不一起出去吃晚饭? 就像朋友一样
What "four of us"?
哪四个?
You and Bob, and me and my girlfriend...
你和鲍伯,我和我的女友…
... Monica.
…摩妮卡
I' m telling you, this guy's perfect for you.
要我说,这小伙绝对适合你
Forget it! Not after your cousin who could belch the alphabet.
算了吧,从你那会啧出字母块的表兄后 我再也不敢领教了
Come on,this guy's great. His name's Bob. He's Angela's...
没骗你，他真的很棒 他叫鲍伯，安琪拉的…
... brother. He's smart, he's sophisticated...
…哥哥.鲍伯简直是太棒了 聪明，成熟
...and he has a real job.
…又有真正的工作
I go on three auditions a month and say l' m an actor,but he's
我呢?我每个月面试三次就称自己是演员
-God help us. -What?
-愿神帮助我们 -什么?
Ugly Naked Guy is laying kitchen tile.
丑陋的裸男在铺厨房磁砖
Look,l' m asking a favor here.
我在求你帮忙
If I do this for her brother, maybe Angela will come back to me.
如果我能为她哥哥做点事 或许她会回到我身旁
What's going on? You go out with tons of girls.
你是怎么了? 你和千百个女人约会
I know,but Angela's different.
我知道,但是安吉拉很不一样
She's like one of a kind, like a snowflake or....
她就像那一种…那种雪花
-Something else like a snowflake? -Yeah,yeah.
-其他像雪花的东西 -是的,是的
Look,I made a huge mistake. I never should've broke up with her.
我犯了天大的错误 我不该和她分手
Will you help me? Please?
愿意帮我吗?求求你
Hold on a sec. You need to not touch any of those.
等等…你能不能不要碰其他的东西
Okay,bye.
没问题，再见
Monica's not coming. It's just gonna be me and Rachel.
摩妮卡不能去了 现在只剩我和瑞秋
Hold on,camper. You've thought this through?
等等，老兄你确定自己仔细想过
It's laundry. The thinking-through is minimal.
只是去洗店没仔细想过
Just you and Rachel? Just you two?
你是说只有你和瑞秋? 只有你们两个?
This is a date. You're going on a date.
这叫约会 你们要去约会
-Uh-uh. -Uh-huh.
-I haven't done that in a while. -ls it a date if she doesn't know?
-我有一阵子没干这个了啊 -她都不知道能算是约会吗?
Yes,absolutely. Saturday night,all rules apply.
当然是的 星期六晚上，什么规则都可以用
What are you saying? I should shave again? Pick up some wine?
你在说些什么呢? 该再刮刮胡子或挑瓶美酒?
Well,you may wanna rethink the dirty underwear.
或许你该再考虑你那肮脏的内衣裤
It's the first time she'll see your underwear. You want it dirty?
因为将她首度见到你的内衣裤 想让她看见你那肮脏的内衣裤吗?
No.
不想
And the fabric softener?
还有衣物柔顺剂
Okay,now what is wrong with my Snuggles?
我的熊宝贝又怎么了?
What? It says I'm a sensitive, warm kind of guy.
这代表我敏感贴心
You know,like a little fuzzy bear.
就像一只毛绒绒的熊宝贝
-I'll pick something else up. -There you go.
-好吧，我在路上买就是了 -这才上道
Thank you.
谢谢
What does Bob look like? Is he tall,short?
鲍伯长什么样? 到底是高还是矮?
Yep.
-Which? -Which what?
-什么? -什么?
-You've never met Bob,have you? -No,but
-你没和鲍伯见过面，对不? -对，可是…
-For all we know,he's horribly -Hey,Joey!
-拜托，这家伙可能相当… 嘿,乔伊
Horribly attractive. I'll be shutting up now.
非常的吸引人. 我闭嘴就是了
Where are they? Where are they?
他们在哪儿?他们在哪儿?
This is nice. We never do anything,just the two of us.
感觉真好，我们俩从未独处过
Great. Maybe tomorrow we can rent a car,run over some puppies.
对，或许明天 我们可以租辆车撞几只小狗
I don't wanna do that.
我不想那样
-Here we go. -Have a good breakup.
-她来了 -祝你有个愉快的分手
-Hey,Janice. -My God,I am so glad you called me.
-珍妮丝 -真高兴你打电话给我
I had the most supremely awful day.
我从来没这么悲惨的一天
That's not good.
不妙
Can I get an espresso and a latte over here?
能端杯浓缩咖啡和拿铁来吗?
We got the proofs from the shoot with the vegetables. They sucked.
我们刚在有蔬菜的那个摄影小站拍了照 但那些蔬菜烂透了
I blew off the afternoon. I went shopping.
我的整个下午就这样毁了 我去逛街购物
And I got you....
然后就为你买…
I'm looking. I'm looking.
我在找…我在找…
I' m looking.
我为你…
-I got you -What?
-我为你… -什么?
-What? -What did you get me there?
-什么? -你帮我买什么?
I got you...
我帮你买…
...these.
…这个
Bullwinkle socks.
布文哥袜
-That's sweet. -I knew you had Rockys.
-真可爱 -我知道你已有洛基
You can wear Bullwinkle and Bullwinkle or Rocky and Rocky,or you can mix.
所以我想你可以穿一双布文哥 或穿一双洛基,或混着穿
Moose and squirrel. Whatever you want.
随你高兴
I'm gonna get another espresso. More latte?
我再去叫一杯浓缩咖啡 想再来一杯拿铁吗?
No,l' m still working on mine.
不用了，我的还没喝完
-That's it? -Yeah,it was really hard.
-这样就搞定了 -是的，你知道这样做很难
-Yeah,the hug looked pretty brutal. -You weren't there.
-没错，那个拥抱真惨烈 -你不在场
-Sorry. -How are things going?
-对不起 -事情处理的怎样?
Going? Things are not going. She got me socks.
这样?分手的事情就这样了. 她给我买了袜子
These go with your Rockys. She really cares about you l' m sorry.
现在你有洛基袜子了啊! 她真的很关心你,对不起
Coming through. Move. Move!
借过，让开…
Excuse me! I was kind of using that machine.
抱歉，我用这台洗衣机
Yeah,well,now you' re kind of not.
是吗?不过现在不是了
But I saved it. I put my basket on top.
但是我占位置了, 我放了篮子在上面
I'm sorry. Is that your basket?
抱歉，这是你的篮子吗?
It's pretty. Unfortunately,I don't see suds!
真漂亮， 但是我没看到洗衣水
What?
什么?
No suds,no save,okay?
没肥皂水就不算保留，行吗?
What's going on?
怎么了?
Nothing. This horrible woman just took my machine.
没什么 这位凶婆娘抢了我的洗衣机
Was your basket on top?
你有把篮子放上面吗?
-Yeah,but there were no suds. -So?
-有，但是没有肥皂水? -然后呢?
-You know,no suds,no save. -No suds,no Excuse me.
-没肥皂水就不算保留 -没肥皂水,抱歉
Hold on a second! This is my friend's machine.
等等 这是我朋友用的机器
Hey,hey,hey! Her stuff wasn't in it!
她的东西没在里面
Hey,hey,hey! That's not the rule,and you know it!
你明知规矩不是这样的
All right. Show's over.
表演结束
Nothing to see here.
没什么好看的
Okay. Let's do laundry.
洗衣服吧
That was amazing! I can't even send back soup.
这简直是太神奇了 我连汤都不敢退
Well,that's because you' re such a sweet,gentle....
因为你是个温柔可爱的
Do you? Do you? Oh,hey. You must need detergent.
你?你? 你得用洗衣粉
-What's that? -Uberweiss.
-那是什么? 乌伯怀斯
It's new. It's German. It's extra tough!
来自德国的新产品 洗净力超强
Rach,are you gonna separate those?
瑞秋，你准备分开洗吗?
Oh,God. Am I being a total laundry spaz?
天哪,我像个洗衣大白痴
Am I supposed to use one machine for shirts and another for pants?
我得用一台洗衬衣 用另一台洗裤子吗?
Have you never done this before?
你没洗过衣服?
Well,not myself. But I know other people that have.
没有，但我认识这样洗过的人
Okay. You caught me. I'm a laundry virgin.
好吧，被你逮到了 我没洗过衣服
Don't worry. I'll use the gentle cycle.
别担心，我会用慢水循环
Basically,you wanna use one machine for all your whites.
你得用一台洗你全部的白衣白衣
A whole other machine for your colors.
另一台洗其他颜色的衣服
And a third for your...
第三台洗…
...delicates. That would be your bras...
…贴身.胸罩和…
...and your underpanty things.
…内裤之类的
These are white cotton panties.
这些棉质的白色内裤呢?
Would they go with whites or with delicates?
与白衣还是贴身衣物一起洗?
That would be a judgment call.
随便你罗
He's so cute!
他好帅
Where did you grow up?
你们在哪儿长大?
-Brooklyn Heights. -Cleveland.
-布鲁克林 -克里佛兰
-How'd that happen? -My God!
-怎么会这样? -天哪!
What?
哎哟
I suddenly had the feeling I was falling.
我突然感到一阵晕眩
But I'm not.
但是没有
So,you and Angela,huh?
你和安琪拉在一起?
-Yep. Pretty much. -You' re a lucky man.
-差不多 -你真幸运
Know what I miss most about her?
知道我最想念她什么?
That cute nibbly noise she makes when she eats.
她轻啃东西的声音
Like a happy little squirrel...
好像是快乐的小松鼠…
...or a weasel.
…或是鼬
-I never really noticed. -Oh,yeah,yeah. Listen for it.
-我倒是没注意过 -以后注意听
Monica. Monica is great.
摩妮卡，摩妮卡很好
Yeah,she is.
没错
But it's not gonna last.
不过不会维持很久
She's too much for me in bed.
我心有余而力不足…在床上
Sexually.
两性之间地
I've gotta tell you,Bob is terrific.
我得告诉你,鲍伯简直是太棒了
Yeah,isn't he?
可不是吗
It's great to meet a smart,funny guy who's emotionally older than 8.
能遇上聪明幽默 心智年龄超过八岁的人真棒
You know what else? He's unbelievable in bed!
知道吗?他在床上更是一流
My brother never even told me when he lost his virginity.
我哥从未告诉我 他何时失去童贞
That's nice.
真好
You can. It's like pulling off a Band-Aid.
你能办到的 这就像是拔绷带一样
Just do it really fast, and then the wound is exposed.
快速拔起…露出伤口
Go! Go!
快走
Hi,Janice.
珍妮丝…
Here we go. I don't think we should go out anymore.
管他的,我想我们不该再交往下去了
All right.
Well,there you go.
我知道了…
Stop it,stop it,stop it.
停下来,停下来….
This isn't about you.
这和你无关
I know! It's about your fear of commitment.
我知道,只是你害怕承诺
I' m not afraid.
我一点也不怕
-Please. -I don't!
-拜托. -我不怕
-I don't! I' m ready to commit anytime. -Really?
-我不怕!我准备好了随时都可以 -真的吗?
I know this is gonna sound stupid...
我知道这听起来很傻…
... but I feel that if I can do this...
…但是我觉得如果我可以做这些
...if I can actually do my own laundry...
…我想如果我可以自己洗衣服的话
...there isn't anything I can't do.
…我就没有办不到的事
That does not sound stupid to me.
我一点都不觉得可笑
The first time I had to cook for myself after Carol left me
就像卡箩离开后,我第一次动手做晚饭
I'm sorry,that's all the time we have. Next on Ross....
抱歉，时间到 接下来到我了
-Uh-oh. -What?
怎么了?
Uh-oh....
Uh-oh, 衣服洗好了
Uh-oh,the laundry's done.
It's a song.
这是一首歌
The laundry song we sing.
我们唱的一首洗衣歌
Uh-oh! The laundry's done
Uh-oh!衣服洗好了
-What's the matter? -Nothing.
-到底怎么了? -没事
The laundry's done
衣服洗好了…
Come on,show me.
罗斯，快给我看…
It's just that you left a red sock with your whites,and now...
好吧，白衣中有一只红袜 所以白衣全变成…
...everything's kind of pink.
…全变成粉红色
Everything's pink?
全变成粉红色?
Except for the red sock, which is still red.
对，但红袜还是红袜
Don't be upset. It can happen to anyone.
抱歉，千万别伤心
But it happened to me.
任何人都可能发生这种事
God,I'm gonna look like a big Marshmallow Peep!
我穿这些看来会像一只粉红猪
What am I doing?
我到底是怎么哪?
My father's right! I can't live on my own.
我爸说得对，我无法独立生活
I can't even do laundry!
我连洗衣服都不会
Something went wrong with Underdog and they couldn't inflate his head.
狗气球出了意外 他的头无法膨胀
So anyway...
于是…
...his head is flopping down Broadway,right?
…于是他的头就落在百老汇
And I'm thinking how inappropriate this is.
我心想这实在太不像话了
Something's in my eye. Could we check it in the light,please?
有东西跑进我眼睛 能到灯下帮我看看吗?
-Oh,my God! -What?
-我的天呀! -怎么啦?
Were we at the same table? It's like...
我们是坐在同一桌吗? 这就像是…
...cocktails in Appalachia.
…阿巴拉契亚的鸡尾酒（太离谱了）
-They' re close. -Close? Her tongue's in his ear.
-他们感情很好 -感情很好?她舌头都伸进了他的耳朵
Like you've never got a little rambunctious with Ross.
你和罗斯就不会有小动作?
Joey,this is sick. It's disgusting. It's...
乔伊，这令人难受了，让人恶心
... not really true' is it?
这不是真的，对不?
Who's to say what's true?
谁说是真的?
-What were you thinking? -l' m not proud of this,okay?
-你到底在想什么? -好吧，我也不喜欢这样
Well,maybe I am a little.
或许有一点
-l' m out of here! -Wait!
-我要走了 -等等
You like him. I want her. He likes you.
你喜欢他,我要她,他喜欢你
-Really? -Yeah.
-Really? -Yeah. -真的? -没错
If we put our heads together, between the two of us...
我想只要我们一起想办法
...we can break them up.
就能让他们分开
I' m sorry. I can't believe I did this.
真是抱歉没想到我会这样
I couldn't stop laughing at your Norman Mailer story.
你的故事让我笑得嘴巴合不拢
Waiter? One more plate of chicken wings over here.
服务生，再来一盘鸡翅
Here's the thing. We're different.
我们是不同类型的人
I'm bing,bing,bing. You' re boom,boom,boom.
我就好像丁丁丁 你就好像梆梆梆
Oh,my God! I' m so sorry!
糟了，抱歉
Are you okay?
你没事吧
It's just my lens. It's my lens.
没事，只是我的隐形眼镜
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
I hit her in the eye! In the eye!
我打中她的眼睛,眼睛
This is the worst breakup in the history of the world!
这是有史以来世上最糟糕的分手
Oh,my God!
我的天
-How many have you had? -I don't know. A million!
-你到底喝了几杯? -我也不知道,一百万杯?
Chandler,easy,easy. Go to your happy place.
钱德，放轻松 快回到你的快乐天堂
-l' m fine,l' m fine. -All right.
-我没事的… -好吧
-l' m not fine. Here she is. -Wait here,okay? Breathe.
-不妙，她回来了 -在这儿等着，深呼吸
-How do you do that? -It's like a gift.
-你是怎么办到的? -我有天赋
We should always break up together.
我每次分手都该找你
I'd like that!
我乐意之至
The clothes are clean. That's the important part.
你已把衣服洗净 现在是重要部份
I guess. Except everything looks like jammies now.
大概吧…只是衣服都成了睡衣
I'm sorry. Excuse me. We had this cart.
抱歉，推车是我们的
I had a 24-inch waist. You lose things.
我的腰围也曾是24寸 你丢东西了吗
Now,come on. Get out of my way.
让开，别挡道
I' m sorry. Maybe I wasn't being clear. This was our cart.
抱歉，或许我没说清楚 这车是我的
There weren't clothes in it!
这上面没有衣服
Hey,hey,hey,hey! Quit making up rules!
你又再乱编规定了
Let go! Come on,it's my cart.
放手,车是我的
Listen,Mitzi,if you want it...
好吧，想用这辆车
...you' re gonna have to take me with it!
你就得推着我一起走
-Yes! Did you see that? -You were incredible.
-我赢了，看见没? -你真是太神奇了
A brand-new woman, ladies and gentlemen.
各位，一位脱胎换骨的新女性
Thank you. I could not have done this without you.
多亏了你我才能办到
More clothes in the dryer?
烘乾机里还有衣服?
-I'm fine. I'm fine. -Are you sure?
-我没事,我没事 -你确定
-Are you sure you' re okay? -Yeah.
-你确定你没事 -是的
-Does it still hurt? -Yeah.
-还疼吗? -是的
What a neat idea! All your clothes match. I' m gonna do this.
真是聪明，衣服颜色都一样 我也要这么做
-How'd it go? -Excellent!
-嘿,怎么样啦? -很好！
We ripped that couple apart and kept the pieces for ourselves.
我们拆散那一对 并将他们占为已有
What a beautiful story.
真是美丽动人的故事
-I'm fine,by the way. -I'm sorry.
-我已经没事了. -对不起
-Where's Chandler? -He needed time to grieve.
-钱德在哪儿? -他需要一点时间疗伤
I' m free! I' m free!
我自由了…我自由了…
That ought to do it.
他应该复原了